honestly I electrolyte by accident and now they have
честно я электролит случайно и вот они
brought down that what
теперь обрушили что что
electrolyte drank electrolyte drank
электролит выпил электролит выпил
electrolyte by accident not on purpose so
электролит случайно не специально так
wait come on so where did you get the electrolyte
подожди давай так где ты взял электролит
And how did you drink it I
И как ты его выпил мне
wonder you thought the water
интересно вы проме воды думал вода
half poured out right the next day
полу сыпались прямо на следующий день
or
или
like right away
как прямо сразу
Hello
Здравствуйте
Zelensky you have a heart You have a very
Зеленский вам сердечко Вы у вас очень
nice smile you have a heart you are a
симпатичная улыбка вам сердечко вы
kind person Zelensky When the
добрый человек зеленски Когда закончится
war ends When you get your teeth inserted then the
война Когда вы зубы вставить тогда и
war will end
война закончится
like you Zelen how are my teeth let's
как и ты Зелен как мои зубы давай
talk normally let's talk normally Where are you from
нормально пообщаемся давай нормально Ты
yourself and what and what are you And what are you wait
откуда сам а что а что ты А что ты
And what do you mean by my teeth
погоди А что ты на мои зубы имеешь в
you just say When the war
виду просто ты же говоришь Когда война
ends I'm just saying when it's like they
закончится Я просто говорю когда это как
say like a cancer on a mountain svisne when
говорят как рак на гор свин когда зубы у
we had teeth You don't see my teeth your teeth
нас был Ты моих зубов не вижу твои зубы
at all what's wrong with your teeth
вообще что там с зубами
show me I don't see we have a proverb like that you
покажи я не вижу у нас пословица есть
just know how they say
такая просто вот знаешь как говорят
When a cancer is on a mountain svisne that's what they say
Когда рак на горе свисне та говорят
when someone asks you some questions you
когда кто-то тебя какими-то вопросами ты
say
говоришь
Cool got it let's get acquainted My
Прикольно понял давайте знакомиться Меня
name is Andrey I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky  Where are you
зовут Андрей я из города Хмельницкий Вы
from I'm from the city of Penza
откуда Я из города Пензы
nyuk Yes, I got it, Penzak Penzak says it right
нюк Да понял пензяк Правильно говорит
I'm 43 years old I'm from Khmelnytskyi, 50
пензяк мне 43 года я хмельничанка летний
years old And you're a Penzak, how old are you,
А вы пензяк скольки летний
8 years old Damn, we're almost the same age I'm 43, well, it'll be 44 already And you're 38, you're I'm only 6 years older We
6 лет старше Мы в принципе ровесники
can basically be considered the same age What do you do for a living What's my
можно считать Да кем работаете Как меня
name Andrey and what's yours Listen Andrey Let's
зовут Андрей и вас как Слушай Андрей
not talk politics, pryaga Let's
Давай не будем политику пряга
just chat What's your name My name is Vova
Вот давай просто поболтаем Тебя как
Vovan Listen, what do you do for a
зовут Меня зовут Вова Вован Слушай ты
living in
кем работаешь в
Ivan, I'm a plumber, I understand Listen What do you
Иван я слесари понял слушай Как ты
think Where is the best medicine in Russia or
считаешь Где лучше медицина в России или
in
в
Europe Politics will come in handy again No, no, that
Европе опять полити пригодится нене не
's just about medicine
это просто про
in the nineties it was in Europe And
медицину в девяностых была в Европе А
now even it seems to me that Russia is better
сейчас даже мне кажется в России лучше
than Europe And how is medicine better in Russia
чем в Европе А чем в России лучше
than in
медицина чем в
Europe Well, earlier in Europe, in the
Европе Ну раньше в Европе вот в
nineties, well, you know,
девяностых годах вот ну максимум знаешь
2005 at the most I remember my
2005 где-то Я помню моему
dd, they did it in my heart, they did it in this one in
дде делали вот в сердце делали в этом в
London now we have  all this all is
Лондоне сейчас у нас всё это всё
happening all is being done all is being transplanted all is
происходит всё делают всё пересаживают
great all is equal it is generally
всё отлично Всё поравнялись это вообще
easy in short 50 to 50 you asked me I
легко короче 50 на 50 ты меня спросил я
answered you
тебе ответил
Yeah I understand it's just that I am such a small
Угу Понял просто я вот такой небольшой
paradox now again a little bit about teeth
Парадокс сейчас снова немножко про зубы
Well this is already about teeth Yes I
будет Ну это уже про зубы Да я вот
was chatting on chatroulette with Germany with
общался в чатрулетке с Германией с
France with Great Britain and there I did not see
Францией с британией и там я не видел
people with a
людей с с
bad jaw in Russia every second one is like that
э плохой челюстью в России каждый второй
Why is it like this
такой Почему
brother in Russia teeth are expensive
так брат в России зубы дорого
teeth are more expensive than getting a
стоят зубы дороже чем ставить
heart you know how much here the
сердце знаешь сколько вот э челюсть
upper jaw costs
стоит верхня
how much in the region of 500000 rubles and I do
сколько в районе 500000 руб а у меня
n't have that kind of money And I have two jaws
таких д бабок нет А у меня две Челюсти
Lower Upper is 500,000 rubles - that
Нижняя Верхняя это 500.000 руб - это
comes out to 5,000
получается 5.000
dollars well I don't know in dollars in
долларов ну я не знаю на доллары
our language I
по-нашему
understood well And what happened to you at 38 years old
понял хорошо А что у тебя вот в 38 лет
so much with your jaw What
случилось так много с челюстью Что
happened to you to tell the truth or to tell the truth
случилось тебе правду сказать или на
Yes the
правду правду Да
truth was an
правду был
assault fought with enemies they knocked out my teeth
штурм дрались с врагами мне выбили зубы
with a butt I mean they knocked out your teeth with a butt you have not
прикладом в смысле прикладом выбили зубы
had them for how many
тебя их нету уже сколько
years since
лет с двадцать второго
22  Yeah, you
года Ага это ты
fought, you had to And where did you
воевал приходилось А где
fight, that's exactly what to say Yes Well, it looks like it wasn't with a butt somewhere while drunk, they
походу там не прикладом где-то по пьяне
probably knocked you out
тебе выбили скорее
honestly Yes, I Lol electrolyte
всего честно да я Лол электролит
by accident Now they've brought down that what
случайно Вот они теперь обрушили что что
electrolyte drank electrolyte drank
электролит выпил электролит выпил
electrolyte by accident not on purpose So
электролит случайно не специально так
wait, come on, where did you get the electrolyte
подожди давай так где ты взял электролит
And how did you drink it I
И как ты его выпил мне
wonder, I just drank it instead of water, I thought it
интересно выпил просто вместо воды думал
turned out to be water, electrolyte, I drank it
вода получился электролит выпил
then Where is
потом де
this electrolyte, what does it
а что это электролит из чего он
consist of There you probably would have all your mouth,
состоит там тебе бы наверное всю ртань
everything would be OK, OK, so I had an operation
всё бы пож так пож так мне операцию
Where did they do the operation So in
сделали Где сделали операцию так в
Kharkov Well, the operation Where did they do it on your
Харькове Ну операцию Где тебе сделали на
stomach, on your
желудке на
throat in Kharkov,
горле харкове
what did they do to you, what kind of
что тебе делали какую
operation did they do
операцию
to your
разрез до
stomach, comrade
желудку товари
Zelensky No, don't give it, we communicate normally with
Зеленский Да не не давай мы нормально с
you normally I'm just
тобой нормально общаемся я просто я
studying How ordinary Russians live Yes, then
изучаю Как живут простые россияне да то
tell me under what circumstances you
расскажи при каких обстоятельствах ты
drank this electrolyte and what happened
выпил этот электролит и что случилось
next You
дальше
just drank it, like, well, you
Просто выпил троит
just took it and drank it How do they drink water
как ну просто взял выпил Как пьют воду
So where, where did it stand, this Electrolyte,
Так где где он стоял этот Электролит в
what did it
чём он
stand in, in a
стоял в
bottle in the
бутылке в
garage A  Why do you need this I'm just
гараже А тебе зачем это просто
curious Well look, right now I'm drinking
интересно Ну вот смотри вот сейчас я пью
bottles this is an
буты это
electrolyte this is
электролит это
not a
н
post here I was sweating to drink and instead of
поста вот я так потел попить а вместо
water I got
воды попался
electrolyte I didn't know it was an electrolyte I drank it
электролит я не знал что это электролит
and that's it And this is where you drank it Well
Я выпил и всё А это где ты его выпил Ну
in someone else's house in someone else's
в чужом доме в чужом
garage in someone else's
гараже в чужом
garage
гараже
you
ты
no I had to go sunflower seeds I had to I had to fill up I filled up I was
нет я должен был семечки ехать мне было
dry
Надо заправлять я заправился меня сушняк
I went to the column there was an hour and a half I looked
Я пошл в колонку стоит полтора я смот
water I took it but it turned out it wasn't water
вода я взял но получилось это не вода
It
Это электролит
was an electrolyte Listen just what's your name Andrey
был Слушай просто как тебя Андрей зовут
Yes Andrey Here's the Russian language you still don't Okay I'm
Да Андрей Вот русский язык ещ ты неб
breeding I'm not Ukrainian I myself from the
Ладно я развожу я не украинец я сам с
trigger Well done
курка
And before myself May It's me Look I'm
А ещё до себя май Это я смотри Это я
trolling on purpose as if I'm
специально так троллю как будто я
Ukrainian I communicate with
украинец общаюсь с
them and then I say ha-ha I'm from Russia
ними а потом говорю ха-ха я из России
yeah you know
да зна
wait you really like fought
подожди ты короче реально типа воевал
or not fought
или не воевал
but had to when what if you don't come to us
а приходилось когда что к нам не
in the Kursk region I
приедешь в курскую область
would be glad to help And what if he doesn't
помочь рад бы А что не
come what's wrong with your hand
приедет что с рукой
highmore what
хаймор что
highmore you know what highmore well show me What What's wrong with
хайр знаешь что хаймор ну покажи Что Что
your hand Yes it's like this Well get up get up Yes look
у тебя с рукой Да она вот так вот Ну
this hand is normal
смотри вот эта рука нормальная
so it doesn't
так это она выш не
rise up So come on tell me what you
поднимается Так а ну расскажи что ты
drank this time I interrupted like well just with a
выпил в этот раз я перебил как ну просто
splinter We were sleeping This is where it was and when
осколком Мы спали Это где было и когда
it
это
was from
было с 3
November 3, 2022 so then it seems like there
ноября 2022 года так тогда ещё вроде Хай
were no High Mars village Rubanovka Kherson
было посёлок рубановка Херсонская
region We were sleeping I can even take photos for now show me show me Well I have it
область Мы спали даже фотки могу пока
on my
покажи покажи Ну у меня в
phone We were sleeping normally a
телефоне Мы спали нормально
former workshop where they make tractors
бывшая мастерская где трактора
there were walls like this you know the
делают там такие вот стены были знаешь в
screen doesn't
экран не
get in the way poltrow
поме полтроу
[music]
[музыка]
He can't
Больше он не
understand anymore I currently have
понимается У меня сейчас короче
category G temporarily unfit I
категория г временно негоден
mean temporarily they still think that you
В смысле временно они ещё считают что ты
can
можешь
move away
отойти
Of course I can still help with something
Конечно я могу ещё помочь чем-нибудь
but how did you get there at all how did you get there for the
а как ты попал вообще как ты туда на
war
войну
mobilization And what did you work as before
мобилизация А кем ты работал до
mobilization
мобилизации
What do you think I don't know
Как думаешь не знаю
tractor driver not
тракторист не
Seriously Seriously
Серьёзно Серьёзно
Rome was
Рим зерно
loading grain and they gave us a hangman
грузил и нас прие повес дали
sign ok let me sign oh well
распишись да ладно давай распишусь
now
о ну сейчас
you'll tell me fairy tales We're going to war
ты сказки расскажешь Мы же на войну едем
Well we went well Novaya Kakhovka Well near
Ну имы поехали ну Новой Каховки Ну около
Novaya Kakhovka we well you know Kakhovka And who do
Новой Каховки нас ну знае Каховка А как
you think is to blame for the fact that your
ты считаешь кто виноват в том что у тебя
arm is now
теперь рука
broken an interesting question
поломана интересный вопрос
Yeah, I don't
Да что-то я тебе не
trust you You don't trust me I think I think That's how
доверяю Ты не доверяю Я считаю я считаю
I think it's Highmore's fault the
Вот вот как я считаю виноват хаймор
rocket Well someone launched this Highmore
ракета Ну кто-то же этот хаймор запустил
And it's not even my problem who this Hair
А даже не мои проблемы кто этот хайр
Zapu let him figure it out and someone
запу пусть разбирается и кто-то ж тебя
launched you into the Kherson
запустил в херсонскую
region me Yes
область меня Да
[music]
[музыка]
launched just the Russian soul how much did they
запустило просто русская душа сколько
pay you for the
тебе выплатили за повреждение
arm injury 50 million
руки 50 млн
dollars Not
долларов Не
seriously Well the order was from the Russian
серьёзно Ну заказ роди Российской
Federation 3 million 3 million for the injury
Федерации 3 ляма 3 млн за ранение
Yes what don't inspire
Да что ты мне не внушает
confidence in me and what do I look like or what Yes you
доверие а что я на похож или что Да ты
just
прям
look like me I'm talking about
похо мне я те гово
you mustache board and such as they do you
тея усы борд да и такое как они делают
know so work like that mustache Bor I'll
знаешь вот работай вот так вот усы Бор я
tell you I  I have this on purpose,
тебе скажу я специально это у меня не
it's not a flag hanging there, it's a picture Like this, well, the
флаг висит это картинка Типа такая
monitor
получается ну в мониторе типа
displays a normal picture like mine,
отображается нормальна картин как у меня
red, white, blue, red Yes, I'm
красно белый Синь красный Да я же типа
doing it on purpose, I'm spreading the word I'm
делаю я специально развожу Я короче
saying that I'm from Ukraine and I start
говорю что я из Украины всё и начинаю им
telling them everything Trump is ditching us and they're
рассказывать Всё нас Трамп сливает и они
like But you know, Trump is ditching us
такие А всё-таки знаешь да трам сливает
Yes, I'm telling them They're all like
Да я им рассказываю Они такие все прям
wow-wow,
вау-вау
damn I'm just, I just know I'm
капец я вот просто я просто знаешь Я им
telling them, look, now America
говорю что смотрите теперь Америка
will take you Ukraine and you'll
заберёт вас Украину и вы будете
live like in America, we'll live yes, they are the ones
жить как в Америке мы будем жить да они
They wanted Yes, and we'll live richly
те Они хотели Да и мы будем жить богато
in Russia Yes, with our medicine Yes, and they
в России Да с нашей медициной Да а они
will with American health insurance
будут с американской страховой медициной
In America, they all walk around without teeth,
В Америке вообще меди они все без зуб
without kidneys, without anything, I'm also from
ходят без почек без ничего я тоже с
America
Америки
Yes, you should have a flag there, I guess,
Да у тебя флаг там походу должен быть
what kind of flag do I have there Well, you have Russia,
какой у меня там флаг Ну у тебя Россия
Russia
Россия
Everything, even swear And now you're in Pen, like,
Всё даже ска А ты сейчас в Пен типа у
in your workshop or something, or what do
себя в мастерской какой-то или что это у
you have, this is for me, I
тебя это
have my own Look, it even
ещё у меня У меня свой Вот смотри даже
says Samko, this is
написано самко это
Penza No, I just got it once, I just have a
Пенза Нет просто раз так получил просто
wife, I have children Are there
жена дети
wives where you live with you  no but there
есть Есть где с тобой живут жены нет а
is a child and the child lives with you No with the
ребёнок есть а ребёнок с тобой живёт Нет
wife or else the wife is divorced I
с женой а то жена жена есть в разводе В
mean Give obs let's
смысле Дай обс
go Russian Russian yes Kursk
давайк русский русский да Курский
I well my wife in short went on a spree while I was on
я ну жена короче загулял пока я был на
my own Well and went
сво Ну и уехал
to another Russian or Tajik she left
другому к русскому или таджику уехала
ru They threw me on my own and the wife hooked up with a
же ру Кинули на сво а жена замутила с
Tatar at that moment yes And we are all
татарином в этот момент да А мы все
Russians That is, I understand correctly while
русские То есть я правильно понимаю пока
Highmore your hand Tatar your
хаймор твою руку татарин твою
wife Well done
жену Молодец
you still have such Russian men that while
ты ещё таких русских мужиков что пока
they there their Highmore
они там их хаймор
themselves
сами
shied away
шарахались
Russians are more good and now like how is
русских больше хорошо а сейчас типа как
your relationship with your wife and with that tour
у тебя отношения с женой и с тем тур
this
этим
Tatar he hasn't tried to
татарином он там не пробовал тебе ещё
break your hand there yet
там руку поломать
We
Мы
Russians forgive our own I
русские своих прощаем
understand With us it's like that we don't have if my son is
понял У нас так у нас нету если мой сын
mine I haven't lost it yet I'll find you
мне Я же ещё не потерял я найду
know how many
ба знаешь сколько
so if you look there are a lot of girls yes And
так если смотрить девчонок много да А
who needs you with such a hand and with such
кому ты нужен с такой рукой и с такими
teeth for example
зубами например
standing in line in line Yes you are there
в очереди стоят в очереди Да ты там
Penza
Пензенский
Casanova well not Penza well yes under
Казанова ну не пенский ну да под
Yes  Listen, here's another question,
Да Слушай а вот тоже такой вопрос
uh, Listen, Wait, Stop, Take off the Kai sign I
ээ Слыш Погоди Стой Сними Кай знак Мне
don't like it, yeah, I'll be sitting there naked,
не нравится да я Я же голый буду сидеть
okay, let's talk, then I'll go change, I have it
Ну договорим я потом пойду переоденусь
on another floor, it's at
это у меня на другом этаже оно
home, I'm doing it like that, specifically to pretend to be a
дома я ж типа так чтобы специально под
Ukrainian, you know, yeah, I guess
украинца косить понимаешь да ты походу
you're not pretending I mean, it's because
смысле Это ты походу потому что у тебя
something slips through your mind, you're not from
что-то проскакивает ты не изн ты из
Kharkov
Харькова
[music]
[музыка]
Yeah, Listen, Van, who did you vote for
Да Слушай Ван А вот ты за кого голосовал
in these
на этих
elections, I mean, in which
выборах в смысле В каких выборах на
presidential elections, where in Ukraine, in Russia,
президентских Где в Украине в России в
in Russia,
России в России
yeah, I voted for
да я голосовал за
Vladislav A, why did I vote for Zankov and you
Влади А почему я занкова голосовал а ты
for Putin,
за Путина
and how do I use him, he's a man, well, how does
а чем я он вот мужик вот ну чем
he use him to hold
чем он вот в кулаке держит
Russia in his fist, how is that, like that,
Россию в кулаке это
Well, what did he do, medicine,
так Ну что он сделал медицину
dentistry, for example, in Russia, and what do you have to do with
стоматологию например в России А что ты
dentistry,
до стоматологии
k, We have a dentist, everything's fine,
к ло У нас стоматолог всё в порядке
I just don't go myself, I'm afraid of
Просто я сам не иду я боюсь
dentists, yeah, we have everything from, do you think
стоматологов Угу У нас всё от ты думаешь
that we don't have medicine in Russia, or what, do
что у нас в России нет медицины что ли у
we have excellent medicine in our countries?  in
нас медицина отличная у нас ных стана за
2 days they go back I just
2 дня обратно идут Просто я сейчас ушёл
retired now I just look what Who from
на пенсию Я просто смотрю что Кто из
Russia with bad zva they are all afraid of the
России с плохими зва они все боятся
dentist here in America in Europe no one is
стоматолога вот в Америке в Европе никто
afraid of the dentist And in Russia everyone here is
не боится стоматолога А в России все у
afraid of dentists
нас боятся стоматологов
stick out And they implant them you see
торчат А у наставляют вживляют понимаешь
we have a new technology we implant
у нас новая технология у нас вживляют
teeth straight living teeth they bead and theirs are whiter than whiter they shine
зубы пря живые зубы ляют а у них белее
smiling they all have veneers my
улыбаются у них у всех винира у меня
relatives implant us
родные нас вживляют
otherwise it
а то вживлять больно
turns out it hurts to implant them I do You let's not break up the
получается делаю Ты давай не разлагать
stop what to ask even I will
остановку что спрашивать даже я те
answer you I understand I understand who you
отвечу понял Понял кем сейчас
work as now with such a hand I don't
работаешь с такой рукой я никем не
work as anyone I sit at home there I make a Lada Priora at
работаю Я сижу дома вон Ладу Приору
home and how much will I send you for platt or
делаю дома а сколько тебе платт или
canan to the front
канан на фронт
how much do you get for
отправлю сколько получаешь по
disability I yes And how much is a dollar now
инвалидности я да А сколько сейчас
I don't know how much our dollar is it's
стоит я не знаю сколько у нас доллар он
already 85 I think it's
уже 85 вроде
fallen Well I get
упал Ну я получаю
47,000 rubles Yes and another 500 dollars well
47.000 рублей Да так ещ 500 долларов ну
I don't know How much is a dollar
вот я не знаю Сколько долларов стоит
because I don't tell you  I trust either ours or
потому что я тебе не доверяю то ли нашим
yours you are some kind of a smart guy It
то вашим ты какой-то шустрый пацан
seems that you already have what
Походу ты короче уже что
SB
те СБ
this is not a flag this is a picture you can't replace it it
это не флаг это картинка её не заменишь
doesn't exist there is no shadow look the shadow doesn't
это не существую тени нет смотри тень не
fall on it I don't have te either this is a
падает на него У меня те нет тоже это
background just a background [ __ ] You see I'm buoy this is an
фон просто фон сри Вот видишь я бую это
electrolyte
электролит
something well I
чтот ну
wonder Listen and what do you think Do
интересно Слушай а вот как ты считаешь
you look younger than 38 or 38
Ты выглядишь моложе 38 лет или на 38
[music]
[музыка]
This is a putka hall Wait what is this you a
Это путка зал Подожди это ты
tractor starts up
что это трактор вон заводится
next to you and what is barking there It
рядом а у тебя что там лает Походу ты
seems that you just let in a whisper wait That is to say you just
шептуна подожди То есть ты только
stank there with such sounds
что навонял там у себя с такими звуками
say that you heard the tractor start And what did you hear bars of the
говори что трактор заводи слышал А что
star come here and Ida wait
ты слышал такты звё иди сюда а Ида
hang for a bit Come on come on now te Let's
погоди повиси чуть-чуть Давай давай
start your tractor come on what then you
сейчас те Давай заведут тебе трактор
won't be able to then climb in
что потом не сможешь потом залез
listen I'm
слуша я
with I'm with
с я
who I know you're
кого я знаю
coming here
иду ты здесь
Dada ses and Yes my mother is what Yes
Дада сес и Да у меня мать какая Да
Europe is cool who's at  you there in short
крутая Европа это кто у тебя там короче
what kind of
что за
Virgo is this Alice not seriously who is this It's
Дева это Алиса не серьёзно кто это Это
my mom I understood And what did she come to the garage
мама моя понял А что она в гараж пришла
or is it not a
или это не
garage what's the difference I'm just
гараж вот те какая разница Просто
interested in sending you the coordinates Well this is
интересно тебе координат скинуть Ну это
not a garage you can see that it's not a garage you can see that
же не гараж видно что не гараж видно что
because they don't make
потому что в гараже на потолке не делают
such
такие
wallpaper on the ceiling in a garage this is a kitchen And this is a house show me show me a
обои это кухня А это дом покажи покажи
house really Well
дом реально
turn around turn around just a
Ну разверни разверни просто
phone fight I see you a Yeah and I you to here you
телефон сеча Я же тебя вижу а Ага а я
show me too Where is she finding and
к вот ты мне тоже покажи Где тея находит
I have a computer it doesn't
а у меня компьютер он не
turn not from the
поворачивается не с
phone how old is mom Move the background
телефона маме сколько лет Пошевели фон
there behind you how old is mom
там за собой маме сколько лет
79 what does it look like for you at
79 это что на тебя получается в
30 STO at 41 oh she gave birth to you at 41 she
30 СТО в 41 о она тебя в 41 родила она
still remembers World War II
ещё Вторую Мировую
how can she have World War II Complete
помнит как она может вторую мир Выполни
years
лет
with What do you think like
с Как ты считаешь типа
Ukraine lives normally without Russia or
Украина живёт нормально без России или
not no And why does Ukraine need Russia wait
нет нет А зачем Украине Россия подожди
Stop slow down that's what
Стой тормози
Ukraine in theory should live
вот что Украина по идее должна жить
separately in general completely separately from
отдельно вообще вообще отдельно от
Russia so it lives that we
России так она и живёт что мы на неё
attacked it no
напали не
wait Ukraine to be
погоди Украина быть
Kherson  fence off the region now
Херсонской область отгородить сейчас
even
даже
Kherson Odessa it is desirable not to fence off
Херсон Одессу желательно е отгородить
from there and let Ukraine live it nobody
оттуда и пусть Украина живёт ей никто не
interferes let it live now Trump will
мешает пусть она живёт сейчас вам Трамп
block the pickaxe and
ещ кирок перекроет и
live m nobody interferes
живите м никто ниче мешает
nothing will be needed you there take from you
нито не будет нужны вам там взять у
What did you ask about this
вас Ты что вот про это
And you know in general I'll
спрашивал А ты знаешь вот вообще Вот
tell you honestly I was there myself Yes
честно тебе скажу Вот сам я там был Да
here in the Kherson region you even
вот Херсонской области те даже посёлок
call the village Rubanovka you can check if
назову рубановка можешь проверить если
you are really from there Well at least what numbers
ты правда оттуда Ну ты хоть номера какие
are showing I'm from Kursk not from Kherson I'm
показывают Я из Курска не из Херсона Я
from
из
Kursk listen carefully I was in Ruban
Курска слушай внимательно Я был в Рубан
Rubanovka the village of Rubanovka near Novo
рубановке посёлок рубановка около Ново
Kakhovka Kherson region I was directly
Каховки Херсонская область мне прямо
told by local residents when we had
местные жители рассказывали когда мы
n't entered there yet
туда ещё не
And then
зашли А потом зашли
we entered me a man One said go men
мы мне мужик Один сказал го мужики
Okay you came a girl was walking here yours
Хорошо вы пришли шла девчонка вот ваша
by the way Not ours she lived there
между прочим Не наша она там жила
a girl of 12 years old were walking I don't know who was
девчонка 12 лет шли я не знаю кто там
walking there three mercenaries three Pole
шли три наёмник три поляк
three he says in the uniform it was unclear they were
три он говорит форме непонятно было они
walking in your uniform with these blue
шли в форме ваший синими вот этими
stripes of theirs  blue and yellow
полосками своими сине-жёлтый
passed she passed them they passed her they
прошли она прошла их они прошли её
said hello everyone they gave her a Kalashnikov in line
поздоровались всё они дали ей в очередь
she fell and why did you directly
Калашникова она упала и зачем ты прямо
see all this You saw all this you
это видел всё Ты видел это всё
press Well then you wait how did they
давишь Ну так ты это подожди как они при
shoot all this in front of you
тебе это всё расстреляли
if they shot her in front of me I would not have You did
её если они при мне расстреляли Я бы Ты
nt tell it like that And how do you
не рассказывал так А откуда ты это
know this like that Where do residents
знаешь так Откуда это житель
tell this A I understand I understand These are your
рассказывают А понял понял Это ваши
grandparents who live there in the Kherson
бабушки дедушки которые там в Херсонской
region
область
and the father of our Orthodox put him on his
живут и папа нашего православного на
knees poured out his throat this is
колени поставили глотку перели это
right horror and tell me they are not a fascist And did
правильно ужас и скажи они не фашист А
you see
ты видел
how you ask
как спрашиваешь
I I know the story that there was a boy in Donetsk
я Я знаю историю что там было в Донецке
in panties on a
мальчика в трусиках
cross Well here and you saw not I know they
кресте Ну вот а ты видел не я знаю
told the whole Donbass about this
рассказывали весь Донбасс про это
spoke with
говорил с
all on
вся на
what Yes you know what you are talking about and I
какую Да ты знаешь о чём ты говоришь и я
know too Listen what do you think where are the
знаю Слушай как ты считаешь где люди
free people And where in Russia or in
свободные А где в России или в
Ukraine Yes and
Украине
we have grown up
езе у нас врос
lets do it lets do
давай так давай
it in the European Union people can change
так в Евросоюзе люди могут поменять
their
своего
ruler in countries in the countries of the European Union
правителя в странах в странах Евросоюза
people can elect their president
люди могут избрать своего президента
Premiere Well yes they can And in
премьера Ну да могут А в
Russia Well not in Russia only
России Да не в России только
Putin Well because we like him Yes we
Путин Ну потому что он нам нравится Да
like him in general a man
нравится он на вообще мужик
super super And what do you know about
у супер супер А что ты знаешь про
Navalny I don't know anything at all
Навального вообще ничего не знаю ящ А
about
про
Zhirinovsky Zhirinovsky is a man too And
Жириновского Жириновский мужик во тоже А
what if Zhirinovsky
чем если бы Жириновский
was he was even a bream Putin was still he would have you
был он даже лещ Путин ещё был он бы вас
now
сейчас
faster we would have already been you know at the borders
быстрее мы уже были бы знаешь у границ
somewhere in Poland
где-то Польше
probably Damn, how did he die Yes at the wrong time
наверное Блин как он умер Да не вовремя
Yes this is for now Putin is patient he tolerates
Да этоже пока Путин терпеливый он терпит
citizens And how do you think who
он граждан А как как считаешь кто
killed Prigozhin who blew up Prigozhin's plane
убил кого кто взорвал самолёт
Yes I'm from Kuna Well what do you think who killed
Да я от куны Ну как ты думаешь кто убил
Prigozhin
пригожина
Well Putin killed
Ну Путин убил
Prigozhin maybe the
пригожина може загорелся просто
engine just caught fire Yes you never know Well Anything can happen
мотор Да мало ли Ну Всяко
Navalny just had a blood clot
бывает у Навального просто тромб
come off
оторвался у
this Prigozhin's engine just
этого пригожина просто мотор
caught fire Well ae
загорелся Ну ае
dawn I'm just watching Navalny
зари я вот просто смот у Навального
nothing happens to Putin come on Putin
случи у Путина не случается ничего давай
Medvedev damn that's what
вот Путин Медведев вот блин вот что у
they have in short nothing catches fire there nothing
них короче там не загорается ничего не
explodes I'm straight  wait wait wait
взрывается я вот прям вот уже погоди
you forgot Kadyrov and
погоди погоди ты забыл Кадыров и
Kadyrov and because they hurt
Кадыров а потому что бо ранит
him like that halos hang over him Angels
ихня вот так над ним висят нимбы Ангелы
hang over him because they
висят над ним потому что они право
do the right thing you are
делают ты
Orthodox Yes you know the 10 commandments I know Well
православный Да 10 заповедей знаешь знаю
tell me don't steal don't
скажи не Укради не
kill I forgot
Убей забыл
better
лучше
Ana
Ана
no I didn't
не это не
forget And that was not Steal but
забыл А это уже было не Укради а Отче
Our Father at least you know how Our Father you know I
наш хоть знаешь как Отче наш знаешь я
pray in my own way Well come on tell me
по-своему молюсь А ну давай скажи
how good a
как хорошая
prayer he he he you know when they
молитва он он он знаеш вот когда те
really press and you when here in your
очень прижмёт и ты по тебя когда вот
own way you will pray it doesn't matter
прит по своему будешь молиться неважно
what kind of God you have Allah or whatever you have
какой у тебя Бог там Аллах или что тебе
you will pray in your own way and I
там ты будешь по-своему молиться и я
pray in my own way he hears you when he
по-своему молюсь он тебя слышит когда он
you here yes I am baptized I am baptized I do
тебя вот здесь вот да я крещён я крещён
not hide I am baptized well and I pray in my
я не скрываю я крещённый ну и молюсь
own way in my soul he and so they
по-своему в душе он и вот у украинцев
stole this soul from the Ukrainians they are now
душу эту украли они сечас
starting
начина
Russian Russian
русский русский
k and what do you have against we ourselves saved
к а что против имеешь мы сами спасали
grandma Babush
бабушку
according to us the granny was wounded and the granny had
Бабуш по нам бабу ранена была а бабушка
nothing to do with
Вообще ни при
it Okay we
чём Ладно мы
Soldiers the granny was lying near no blood
Солдаты бабушка валялась у не крови
Normal we dragged her here to the
Нормально мы её сюда притащили в
hospital we generally we what we what you what do you
госпиталь мы вообще мы что мы что вы что
think of us We what with such we don't
на нас думаете Мы что с такие мы не
wait you Now just for
подожди ты Сейчас только что за
scratching do you hear Streamer just
чесал слышишь Стример только что
did this
делал
I tucked my leg three ku got it got it all
так я ногу заправлял три ку понял понял
but like this
а вот
I do Yes Listen what do you think
так я де Да Слушай а как ты считаешь
why Russia has oil gas gold
почему вот Россия имеет нефть газ золото
diamonds but lives poorer than
алмазы а живут беднее чем
Europe and who will tell you that poorer than
Европа а кто тебе скажет что беднее чем
in Europe I
в Европа по тебе
see interesting
вижу интересно
people you what they pump you with there Tell me pierced with
люди вас что там качают чем Расскажи
oranges and rarely with earth
апельсинами наколотые и редко земельными
metals you seem to have a
металлами
trunk there what do you think we live like that or what Yes Well
транк вы что думаете мы так живём что ли
I see how you
Да Ну я же вижу как ты
live And who told you that I live here
живёшь А кто тебе сказал что я здесь
I didn't say you live here I see
живу Я же не сказал здесь живёшь Я вижу
how you live your face at 38 your teeth
как живёшь твоё лицо в 38 лет твои зубы
at 38 Your hand at 38 your
в 38 лет Твоя рука в 38 лет твоя
environment at 38 this beer and so
обстановка в 38 лет вот это пиво и так
on
дальше
Yes and you
Да а
know here I am  I'll tell you one thing, I
знаешь вот я тебе Умно одну вещь скажу
don't know, you'll understand, you won't understand, but we live
не знаю поймёшь не поймёшь зато мы живём
happily, we don't need anything,
счастливо ничего не
Europe, so if you don't need anything,
надо Европа то если вам ничего не надо
why did you go to Ukraine, so you
что же вы полезли в Украину чтобы она
need it, you caught it, after all, I caught it, so it's in vain that I
надо поймал всё-таки поймал я значит зря
show the numbers, after all, you're right,
номера показываю всё-таки ты прав
yes, I'll reveal this, I'm Ukrainian,
Это да вскрою Я украинец
these numbers are a trap for gullible
это номера ловушка для доверчивых
Rojans, Look, I have another cat
роян Смотри у меня ещё такой кот есть
who curses everyone who fought
который проклинает всех кто воевал
against
против
Ukraine, wait, I'll find my god, come on,
Украины погоди сечас ко своего найду
give me a second,
бого давай давай секунду
Come on, he caught me that I was from Ukraine,
Давай он спалил меня что я из Украины
he's just a genius
это просто гений
detective, And I have a Russian combat cat,
сыщик А у меня вот русский боевой кот
come on,
иди-ка
eyes, come on, Smile at
глаза ну-ка Улыбнись на
him, Listen, but seriously, where
него Слушай а серьёзно Где ты
are you, yes, in Kursk, in Kursk, I just sometimes get
находишься да в Курске в Курске Я просто
so fed up with you that I'm
ты меня так задол бываешь что я короче
from Ukraine, damn, I'm telling you, Okay, let it be
из Украины то блин Я тебе говорю Хорошо
from
пусть будет из
Ukraine in Kursk with this lag, Well, I don't
Украины в Курске с этим лагом Ну я не
go with the lag, in short, there's a picture hanging
хожу с лагом это короче картинка висит
here,
тут
narrowing, narrowing, not narrowing
сужа сужа не сужа
occupied well you with this
оккупирована ну ты же с этим
lag aren't you
лагом не
bro
братан ли
you're either with us or against
с ты либо с нами либо против
us I'm for Russia but against pu
нас Я за Россию но против пу
I want democrats to come and
Я хочу чтобы демократы пришли и
break it up into different states why for
развалили её на разные государства зачем
example should we from Kursk region feed
например нам Курской области кормить
your Samara
вашу самарскую
we are in Kursk region we have agriculture
мы в Курской области там у нас сельское
industry there and you Why the
хозяйство промышленность А у вас Зачем
hell should we support
нам блин содержать
you interesting
вас интересный
question What do you have there We have
вопрос Что у вас там У нас
industry we have agriculture do you have
промышленность у нас сельское хозяйство
ears or something You
слы что ли Ты мне
[music]
[музыка]
tell me skow how many fields are there in Kherson
расскажи сков а сколько в Херсонской
region Now tell me I don't know
области полей Вот расскажи мне я не знаю
I'm not from Kherson I'm from Kursk
я не из Херсона Я из Курска А мне
And you're telling me and what do you mean that
рассказываешь и Ты что имеешь в виду то
yes you I've screwed up
что да ты Я же затроил
Sorry did you just realize what you said yes
Извини ты сейчас сам понял что сказал да
You look like you're from what planet at all
Ты походу это ты с какой планеты вообще
from the planet
с планеты
Iron thing look like yes what did you say now
Железяка походу да что ты сказал сейчас
there with Kursk there is something there I'm from
там с Курской там что-то там я из
Kursk region and we feed your Samara
Курской области так и мы вашу самарскую
yes And do you even know
да А ты в курсе вообще
that in every
что в каждом
region Well you look like It's not me that you have in
реги Ну ты походу Это не я что у вас в
every
каждом
region No I don't mean
регионе Да не я имею в виду
it's here Everything is fine  In each region
это тут Нормально всё В каждом регионе
what are
что
you driving
гонишь
everything turned off the roulette of this rich
всё отключила рулетка этого
man about the store
богача о магад
nerve to endure them It's just brutal
нерво вытерпеть их Это просто жесть
these shabby toothless armless people sit
сидят вот эти облезлый беззубые безруки
in poverty and climb into Ukraine to
в нищете и лезут в Украину ещё что-то
decide something else like a squeak comment a letter on y
решать лайк писка комент пись на й
Telegram right now axis win and
Telegram прям зараз ось вин а
while this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through scarg or in ny ban and very
нас через скарг ор в ньй бан и дуже
many videos I do not show people at times do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams That is why
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
we Mali operational links are
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
written right now and while there are in Telegram
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
OKM videos there is also interesting and useful
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are obliged to you three
информация и мы повинни з вами трима
constant operational links independently
постийний оперативный звязок незалежно
in that chi will show you about this YouTube
в того чи покаже вам про це YouTube
Glory to Ukraine subscribe
Слава Украине подпишись